Boston Dispensary Records MS214
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Superintendent records, 1823 -- 1911; MS214.013
  - Bills and receipts - Engraving copper plate and printing patient tickets, 1798; MS214.013.024.00226 (Box 24, Folder 226)
  - Bills and receipts - Account books, 1797; MS214.013.024.00227 (Box 24, Folder 227)
  - Bills and receipts - Furnishings, 1797; MS214.013.024.00228 (Box 24, Folder 228)
  - Bills and receipts - Truss, 1805; MS214.013.024.00229 (Box 24, Folder 229)
  - Bills and receipts - Electrical machine and repairs, 1811 -- 1812; MS214.013.024.00230 (Box 24, Folder 230)
  - Bills and receipts - Nursing, 1814; MS214.013.024.00231 (Box 24, Folder 231)
  - Bills and receipts - Collecting subscriptions, 1816 -- 1828; MS214.013.024.00232 (Box 24, Folder 232)
  - Bills and receipts - Commission on collection of subscriptions, 1830 -- 1835; MS214.013.024.00233 (Box 24, Folder 233)
  - Bills and receipts - Advertising, 1820 -- 1835; MS214.013.024.00234 (Box 24, Folder 234)
  - Bills and receipts - Printing, 1817 -- 1819; MS214.013.024.00235 (Box 24, Folder 235)
  - Bills and receipts - Furnishings, 1818 -- 1829; MS214.013.024.00236 (Box 24, Folder 236)
  - Bills and receipts - Medical equipment, 1834; MS214.013.024.00237 (Box 24, Folder 237)
  - Bills and receipts - Medical equipment - Electrical machine repair, 1818 -- 1820; MS214.013.024.00238 (Box 24, Folder 238)
  - Bills and receipts - South Boston Bridge toll, 1827; MS214.013.024.00239 (Box 24, Folder 239)
  - Bills and receipts - Advertising, 1836 -- 1855; MS214.013.024.00240 (Box 24, Folder 240)
  - Bills and receipts - Printing and distribution of notices, 1836 -- 1855; MS214.013.024.00241 (Box 24, Folder 241)
  - Bills and receipts - Contractors, masonry, whitening for office, 1846 -- 1851; MS214.013.024.00242 (Box 24, Folder 242)
  - Bills and receipts - Furnishings and carpentry, 1845; MS214.013.024.00243 (Box 24, Folder 243)
  - Bills and receipts - Glassware and pottery, 1843 -- 1848; MS214.013.024.00244 (Box 24, Folder 244)
  - Bills and receipts - The Needle-Woman's Friend Society "Making Towels", 1851; MS214.013.024.00245 (Box 24, Folder 245)
  - Bills and receipts - Nursing, 1844 -- 1845; MS214.013.024.00246 (Box 24, Folder 246)
  - Bills and receipts - Nursing, 1846; MS214.013.024.00247 (Box 24, Folder 247)
  - Bills and receipts - Utilities - Boston Gaslight, 1846 -- 1851; MS214.013.024.00248 (Box 24, Folder 248)
  - Bills and receipts - Commission on collections, 1860 -- 1869; MS214.013.024.00249 (Box 24, Folder 249)
  - Bills and receipts - Advertising and printing, 1856 -- 1859; MS214.013.024.00250 (Box 24, Folder 250)
  - Bills and receipts - Advertising, 1860 -- 1871; MS214.013.024.00251 (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - Bills and receipts - Stationers and printers, 1856 -- 1859; MS214.013.024.00252 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - Bills and receipts - Printers, stationers, and mailing, 1860 -- 1868; MS214.013.024.00253 (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - Bills and receipts - Engraving seal, 1870; MS214.013.024.00254 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Bills and receipts - Janitorial and day labor, 1856 -- 1860; MS214.013.024.00255 (Box 24, Folder 255)
- Treasurer records, 1796 -- 1916; MS214.014
  - Maintenance and janitorial receipts, 1861 -- 1864; MS214.014.017.00001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ice, coal, and sand bills and receipts, 1856 -- 1870; MS214.014.017.00002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bennet St. Installation of gas, heating, and kitchen equipment receipts, 1856 --1858; MS214.014.017.00003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Furnishings and maintenance of room bills and receipts, 1857; MS214.014.017.00004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Furnishings bills and receipts, 1860 -- 1869; MS214.014.017.00005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Furnishings, barber's chair bills and receipts, 1863; MS214.014.017.00006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, wall safe, timepiece, etc., 1860 -- 1864; MS214.014.017.00007 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Tooth forcepts, hand and forearm splints bill, 1856; MS214.014.017.00008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Foot apparatus and medical equipment receipt, 1860; MS214.014.017.00009 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Apothecary scales receipts, 1860 -- 1869; MS214.014.017.00010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Artificial limb repair receipt, 1867; MS214.014.017.00011 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Medical supplies and trusses, 1853 -- 1860; MS214.014.017.00012 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Medical equipment bills and receipts, 1862 -- 1869; MS214.014.017.00013 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Medical equipment and clinical supplies receipts, 1869 -- 1875; MS214.014.017.00014 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Housekeeping and laundry bills and receipts, 1856 -- 1869; MS214.014.017.00015 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Laundry receipts, 1869 -- 1879; MS214.014.017.00016 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Cab fare receipt, 1860; MS214.014.017.00017 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Services of girl receipt, 1860; MS214.014.017.00018 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Central Office services receipt, 1891; MS214.014.017.00019 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Doorman service receipts, 1869; MS214.014.017.00020 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Boston Waterworks pipe installation receipt, 1856; MS214.014.017.00021 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Boston Waterworks receipts, 1862 -- 1868; MS214.014.017.00022 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Boston Waterworks bill, 1879; MS214.014.017.00023 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - City of Boston Superintendent of Streets bill, 1861; MS214.014.017.00024 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Collecting Subscriptions receipts, 1879 -- 1880; MS214.014.017.00025 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Advertising receipts, 1877 -- 1879; MS214.014.017.00026 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Stationary bills and receipts, 1876 -- 1879; MS214.014.017.00027 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Janitor receipts, 1878 -- 1880; MS214.014.017.00028 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Ice, coal and gas receipts, 1877 -- 1883; MS214.014.017.00029 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Furnishings receipts, 1877 -- 1879; MS214.014.017.00030 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Furnishings bills and receipts, 1883; MS214.014.017.00031 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Speaking tube installation receipt, 1883; MS214.014.017.00032 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Payments to architects, 1883; MS214.014.017.00033 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Contract with contractors for new bids, 1883; MS214.014.017.00034 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Contractor accounts, 1883; MS214.014.017.00035 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence with contractors regarding payment, 1883; MS214.014.017.00036 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Checks to contractors, 1883; MS214.014.017.00037 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Maintenance and contractor supplies receipts, 1883; MS214.014.017.00038 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Photoelectrotype of building receipt, 1883; MS214.014.017.00039 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Medical supplies receipts, 1877 -- 1878; MS214.014.017.00040 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Glassware and crockery receipts, 1877 -- 1883; MS214.014.017.00041 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Linens bills and receipts, 1875 -- 1879; MS214.014.017.00042 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Boston Gaslight receipts, 1877; MS214.014.017.00043 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Perkins Institute for the Blind fiber mats receipts, 1849 -- 1916; MS214.014.017.00044 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - X-ray tubes receipts, 1916; MS214.014.017.00045 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - City of Boston water bill, 1916; MS214.014.017.00046 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Extermination service receipts, 1916; MS214.014.017.00047 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Supplies from Jordan Marsh Co., 1915; MS214.014.017.00048 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Instructive District Nursing Association receipts, 1915; MS214.014.017.00049 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - 1st Treasurer's Report for Boston Dispensary, William Smith, 1797; MS214.014.018.00001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, William Smith, 1798 -- 1800; MS214.014.018.00002 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, William Smith, 1801 -- 1805; MS214.014.018.00003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's Accounts, William Smith, 1806 -- 1809; MS214.014.018.00004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Edward Phillips, 1810 -- 1812; MS214.014.018.00005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1813 -- 1815; MS214.014.018.00006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1816 -- 1820; MS214.014.018.00007 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1821 -- 1823; MS214.014.018.00008 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1824 -- 1828; MS214.014.018.00009 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1829 -- 1832; MS214.014.018.00010 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1833 -- 1835; MS214.014.018.00011 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer's Accounts, Gideon Snow, 1837 -- 1839; MS214.014.018.00012 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Gideon Snow, 1840 -- 1844; MS214.014.018.00013 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's Reports, George Bigelow, 1845 -- 1847; MS214.014.018.00014 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1848 -- 1850; MS214.014.018.00015 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Edward Blake, 1851 -- 1854; MS214.014.018.00016 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Edward Blake, 1855 -- 1859; MS214.014.018.00017 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Edward Blake, 1862 -- 1863; MS214.014.018.00018 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Francis Parker, 1864 -- 1866; MS214.014.018.00019 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1867 -- 1868; MS214.014.018.00020 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Treasurer's Report, Francis Parker, 1871 -- 1874; MS214.014.018.00021 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1875 -- 1877; MS214.014.018.00022 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's Report, Francis Parker, 1878; MS214.014.018.00023 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Treasurer's Report, Arthur Lincoln, 1884 -- 1885; MS214.014.018.00024 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Arthur Lincoln, 1881 -- 1883; MS214.014.018.00025 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Arthur Lincoln, 1887 -- 1890; MS214.014.018.00026 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Arthur Lincoln, 1891 -- 1893; MS214.014.018.00027 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Treasurer's Reports, Arthur Lincoln, 1894 -- 1898; MS214.014.018.00028 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer's Report, Arthur Lincoln, 1903; MS214.014.018.00029 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Legal - Court Act allowing Boston Dispensary to hold additional capital, 1852; MS214.014.018.00030 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Bills and receipts - Receipts for purchase of stock in banks and insurance companies, 1807 -- 1821; MS214.014.018.00031 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Treasurer - stock in railroad, 1850; MS214.014.018.00032 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Treasurer's correspondence - re: Stock in Neponset Bridge, 1859; MS214.014.018.00033 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Treasurer bank books, 1812 -- 1813; MS214.014.018.00034 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Checks, 1814 -- 1817; MS214.014.018.00035 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Treasurer checks, 1857; MS214.014.018.00036 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Receipt for interest on loan - Lee, Higgins and Co., 1840; MS214.014.018.00037 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Treasurer - pass book - N.E. Trust Co., 1879 -- 1883; MS214.014.018.00038 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Auditor's report, 1865; MS214.014.018.00039 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - List of Contributors, 1806; MS214.014.024.00001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Individual Contributions, 1807; MS214.014.024.00002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Subscriber's List - Printed 5 sheets, 1809; MS214.014.024.00003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - List of Contributors, 1808; MS214.014.024.00004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Board letters - S. Higginson, Jr. appeal for funds, 1809; MS214.014.024.00005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Letter - Dr. Coffin recommends Paul Revere as subscriber, 1815; MS214.014.024.00006 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Contributor letter for Gideon Snow, Treasurer, 1818; MS214.014.024.00007 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Letters - to Treasurer including Gideon Snow re: collector of contributions, 1819; MS214.014.024.00008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Contributors, 1826; MS214.014.024.00009 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Contributors, 1827; MS214.014.024.00010 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Contributors, 1828; MS214.014.024.00011 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Subscribers - Annual Abstract with signatures of subscribers, 1827; MS214.014.024.00012 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Letters of appeal, draft of circular letter, 1828; MS214.014.024.00013 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Appeal, 1828; MS214.014.024.00014 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Subscribers (partial list - new subscribers), 1828; MS214.014.024.00015 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Contributors, 1833; MS214.014.024.00016 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Secretary to Board - acknowledgement of contribution by Snelling, 1833; MS214.014.024.00017 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Contributors, 1833; MS214.014.024.00018 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Subscribers, 1838 -- 1839; MS214.014.024.00019 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Subscribers, 1839; MS214.014.024.00020 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Contributors, 1840; MS214.014.024.00021 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Subscribers, 1841; MS214.014.024.00022 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Subscribers, 1842; MS214.014.024.00023 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Subscribers, 1843; MS214.014.024.00024 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Contributors, 1844; MS214.014.024.00025 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Subscribers, 1846; MS214.014.024.00026 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Circular - re: ticket holdings, 1849; MS214.014.024.00027 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Subscribers list, $5-$10 contributions, 1850; MS214.014.024.00028 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Treasurer George Bigelow - Correspondence - re: discontinued Subscribers, 1850; MS214.014.024.00029 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Fundraising circulars, 1856; MS214.014.024.00030 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - John Moore - letter with contribution, 1858; MS214.014.024.00031 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Appeals - letter and memo, George Thayer, 1859; MS214.014.024.00032 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Subscription - Hemmenway, 1861; MS214.014.024.00033 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Subscribers, 1870; MS214.014.024.00034 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Contributors - list of descendants of original subscribers, 1913; MS214.014.024.00035 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Receipts - donations from R.C. Winthrop, $50, 1874; MS214.014.024.00036 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Contributions - Arlington St. Church, "Hospital Sunday", 1874; MS214.014.024.00037 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Contributions - Ridder, Peabody and Co., "Hospital Sunday" and other donations, 1875; MS214.014.024.00038 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Acknowledgement - Receipt of $1.00 from Patient for medicine (contribution or voluntary payment), 1878; MS214.014.024.00039 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Donations - Montifiore Fund, 1881; MS214.014.024.00040 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Dearborn, Will, Printed 1838 with letter, H. Plympton, MS214.014.024.00041 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Dearborn, Will - printed 1839 - presented by H. Plympton, MS214.014.024.00042 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Letter by H. Plymton and article, "Mercantile Journal", 1838-12-28; MS214.014.024.00043 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Dearborn - Nathanial Dearborn, re: sale of estate, 1840; MS214.014.024.00044 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Dearborn - bill for investigating will, 1843; MS214.014.024.00045 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Dearborn - Legal opinion, William Gray, attorney, 1843-12-02; MS214.014.024.00046 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Dearborn - correspondence - John Dearborn - list of divorces of father's estate with their respective ages - correspondence, re: property, 1843 -- 1844; MS214.014.024.00047 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Dearborn - agreement of heirs to sell, 1844-12-29; MS214.014.024.00048 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Dearborn - H. Plympton - Correspondence - re: measurements and survey of Theater Alley Estate, sale and price of estate, 1844; MS214.014.024.00049 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Dearborn - H. Plympton - Correspondence, 1845 -- 1846; MS214.014.024.00050 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Dearborn - Committee on sale of estate - report, 1846-01-09; MS214.014.024.00051 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Dearborn - William Minor, Oct. 1846 - Correspondence re: sale and mortgage of estate, MS214.014.024.00052 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Bequests - Dearborn - Indenture of Estate, 1846; MS214.014.024.00053 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Dearborn, H. Plympton, re: release of Mortgage, 1848; MS214.014.024.00054 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Dearborn - William Minot - re: mortgage of Theater Alley, 1848; MS214.014.024.00055 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Dearborn - G.W. Gerrish - sale of estate, 1848; MS214.014.024.00056 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Dearborn - Correspondence - George Richardson, re: mortgage of Theater Alley Property, 1851 -- 1852; MS214.014.024.00057 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Treasurer's fee for investment of Dearborn Estate, 1852-10; MS214.014.024.00058 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Bequests - Dearborn - Correspondence - H. Plympton, 1852; MS214.014.024.00059 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Dearborn - Trustee report, 1852; MS214.014.024.00060 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Dearborn - Map of Theater Alley Lots, 1852-03-13; MS214.014.024.00061 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Dearborn - Interest on Estate, 1852; MS214.014.024.00062 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Dearborn - Correspondence re: Dearborn's heirs, 1859; MS214.014.024.00063 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Legal fees - Examination of deeds re: Richardson Mortgage, 1868; MS214.014.024.00064 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Avon Place estate - fee for drawing and copping lease, 1869; MS214.014.024.00065 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Dearborn - Memo on income, 1871; MS214.014.024.00066 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Dearborn - Bill for legal services, 1878; MS214.014.024.00067 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Payment to Hannah Dearborn for Avon St. property, 1878; MS214.014.024.00068 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Phillips correspondence, 1860; MS214.014.024.00069 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Bequests - Abigail Loving Estate and copy of will with correspondence, 1865; MS214.014.024.00070 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Receipts - Estate of Nabby Joy, 1871 -- 1876; MS214.014.024.00071 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Bequests - Abbot Lawrence Estate, 1871; MS214.014.024.00072 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Bequests - James Reed, 1871; MS214.014.024.00073 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Bequests - Hemmenway St., 1877; MS214.014.024.00074 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Bequests - Mary Wigglesworth, 1882; MS214.014.024.00075 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Receipts - Legal services and fees for various estates, 1870 -- 1878; MS214.014.024.00076 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Receipts - Fees for examining estate, 1878 -- 1879; MS214.014.024.00077 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Bills and receipts - Services of constables and cleaners attending chapel and house meetings, 1813; MS214.014.024.00078 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Messenger service, 1827 -- 1828; MS214.014.024.00079 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Payment for Good Samaritan sign board, 1829; MS214.014.024.00080 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Bills and receipts - Stationers, 1870 -- 1875; MS214.014.024.00081 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Good Samaritan sign removal and cleaning, 1839 -- 1856; MS214.014.024.00082 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Bill for painting and guiding Good Samaritan sign, 1859; MS214.014.024.00083 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Receipts - Janitor's services, 1873; MS214.014.024.00084 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Receipts - Contractors, 1856 -- 1868; MS214.014.024.00085 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Receipts - Contractors, 1861 -- 1870; MS214.014.024.00086 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Receipts - Bennet and Ash Streets interiors and furnishings, 1856 -- 1859; MS214.014.024.00087 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Bennet Street - Deduction for heating of rooms, 1890; MS214.014.024.00088 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Bills and receipts - linens, 1856 -- 1875; MS214.014.024.00089 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Receipts - temporary city home for wood, 1875 -- 1879; MS214.014.024.00090 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Receipts - Miscellaneous furnishings, 1877 -- 1885; MS214.014.024.00091 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Receipts - Contractors, 1877 -- 1880; MS214.014.024.00092 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - District Manager's summary, 1837; MS214.014.024.00093 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Accounts -- Whipple, 1848; MS214.014.024.00094 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence regarding districts changes, 1851; MS214.014.024.00095 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Statistics on patients, 1844 -- 1852; MS214.014.024.00096 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Boston Dispensary By-laws, 1855 -- 1858; MS214.014.024.00097 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Report of the Executive Committee regarding the appointment of S. Green, 1866; MS214.014.024.00098 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Board reports, 1830; MS214.014.024.00099 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Dr. John Coffin, resignation, 1815; MS214.014.024.00100 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Dr. Nathaniel Frothingham, resignation, 1852; MS214.014.024.00101 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Dearborn, H. Plympton, re: character of D. Dearborn for history of Boston Dispensary, 1858; MS214.014.024.00102 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Henry Plympton - Acceptance as member of Board, 1859; MS214.014.024.00103 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence - Sammuel Max, re: board meeting and Dr. R. Lawrence's History, 1859; MS214.014.024.00104 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence - Massachusetts Historical Society, re: "Belknap letter," Philidelphia Dispensary, 1860; MS214.014.024.00105 (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence - National Quarentine and Sanitary Convention, 1860; MS214.014.024.00106 (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence - Complaint, re: Tremont St. Physician - by Benard O'Kam, 1860; MS214.014.024.00107 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Facsimile of Belknap Letter, Philadelphia Dispensary, re: funds for establishment of dispensary from sale of book, 1790; MS214.014.024.00108 (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence - Gideon Snow acknowledges $300 payment from committee, 1834; MS214.014.024.00109 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Treasurer - Correspondence Gideon Snow, re: gift of plate, resignation, 1843 -- 1844; MS214.014.024.00110 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Children's Department, Summary of statistics and report, 1909; MS214.014.024.00111 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Bills and receipts - Miscellaneous silver bowl for Gideon Snow, 1844; MS214.014.024.00112 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Dearborn - correspondence, H. Plympton, re: "wood carving", 1839-07; MS214.014.024.00113 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Letter, re: Good Samaritan engraving and signboard, 1858 -- 1859; MS214.014.024.00114 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Dearborn, H. Plympton, re: Peale Painting, 1858; MS214.014.024.00115 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Rembrant Peale Portrait, given by Dearborne Estate - Letter acknowledging gift and explanation of painting by Henry Plympton, 1858 -- 1859; MS214.014.024.00116 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Bills and receipts - Salaries of Staff - Secretary, $100, 1844 -- 1845; MS214.014.024.00117 (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Wm. Debon, Secretary, Salary, 1855; MS214.014.024.00118 (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Staff Salaries - John B. Alley, 1837; MS214.014.024.00119 (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - E. Blake - Salary, 1837; MS214.014.024.00120 (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Receipt - Salary, H. F. Damon, 1864 -- 1865; MS214.014.024.00121 (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Receipt - Salary, S. A. Green, 1866 -- 1871; MS214.014.024.00122 (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Bills and Receipts - Painting signboard, 1802; MS214.014.024.00123 (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Subscribers' Tickets with Good Samaritan Logo, undated; MS214.014.024.00124 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Subscribers' Tickets, 1850 -- 1857; MS214.014.024.00125 (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - List of subscribers - Summary, 1798; MS214.014.024.00126 (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Contributors Certificates, 1797 -- 1856; MS214.014.024.00127 (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Subscribers List, 1800; MS214.014.024.00128 (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Subscribers, 1805; MS214.014.024.00129 (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - List of property and stock deposited at the Massachusetts Bank, 1830 -- 1844; MS214.014.024.00130 (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence - Board to Treasurer - George Thayer Secretary to Gideon Snow Treasurer, note re: Boston Dispensary Stock in Neponset Bridge and note, re: property of physicians in Boston Dispensary, 1843; MS214.014.024.00131 (Box 24, Folder 131)